<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="hugs">
        <item>Yes you can. Don\'t ya ever don\'t ya ever give in ♡</item>
        <item>Always always always make any self-judgement in daylight.\nWe are all a little worse for wear at night-time.</item>
        <item>Hold on!!! You can get through this</item>
        <item>My most loving, caring, squeezing, encouraging hugs to you my dear, you can do it ♡</item>
        <item>Sending huge, enormous, irritatingly large hugs!</item>
        <item>You\'re not a failure you\'re just going through a harsh time. Take care.xoxo</item>
        <item>You win some, you lose some (: the only time you\'ll always fail is when you never try.</item>
        <item>Remember to be compassionate to everyone, including yourself ♡</item>
        <item>hold on,\nyou\'ve come so far!</item>
        <item>\'Failure isn\'t fatal. Success isn\'t forever. What matters is the strength to get back up again\' :)</item>
        <item>Glad you\'re here! :)</item>
        <item>You deserve a life you enjoy, and I have faith that you will have it.</item>
        <item>Sending you strength!</item>
        <item>Sending you so much love and strength along with my biggest protective hugs.</item>
        <item>Much love over to you, my dear, along with my biggest soothing hugs.</item>
        <item>Sending huge protective hugs and hope you\'ll feel better soon ♡</item>
        <item>*hugs* I hope you feel better</item>
        <item>Stress-free hugs x</item>
        <item>It doesn\'t have to be perfect, sometimes it just needs to be done.</item>
        <item>You are brave ♡</item>
        <item>Don\'t give up. It\'s just a bump in the road. :)</item>
        <item>Small victories become big victories x</item>
        <item>Keep going! Trying is the most important thing :)</item>
        <item>You\'ve come a long way. Don\'t give up.</item>
        <item>You don\'t have to try to be strong alone - is there anyone who you can talk to?</item>
        <item>So many people love you even if you can\'t see it at this time. </item>
        <item>Hope whatever your going through will improve soon! *Extra Big Comforting Hugs*</item>
        <item>Hope you get better. Lots of love to you.</item>
        <item>Lots of love and hugs xx</item>
        <item>You can do this, you are stronger than you think and you have the skills to handle it!</item>
        <item>You are special and there is no one who could ever replace you:)</item>
        <item>Try to be as critical of your critical thoughts as they are of you</item>
        <item>*GIGANTIC HUGS*</item>
        <item>You can give up - but give up your pain, the thoughts and emotions that are hurting you.</item>
        <item>Just keep moving forward, everything at some point just becomes a memory.</item>
        <item>You can do it! ♡</item>
        <item>Your feelings are valid ♡</item>
        <item>We can all learn from our failures and move forward.</item>
        <item>Nothing is as disastrous as we believe.</item>
        <item>Don\'t ignore the light in times of darkness. It\'s there. You just can\'t reach it yet</item>
        <item>You\'ll get through this :-)</item>
        <item>You are perfect just with issues</item>
        <item>You\'ll make it. I\'m sure. Crossing my fingers for you</item>
        <item>Huge supportive hugs</item>
        <item>It will get better again. Try to keep some hope xx</item>
        <item>Sending loads of cuddly, comforting hugs.</item>
        <item>I believe in you *hugs*</item>
        <item>It\'s the small steps that bring you forward</item>
        <item>Sometimes it can be refreshing to just let it all out. I hope you are okay x</item>
        <item>You will get through this. Hold on xx</item>
        <item>Just face a bit at a time, whatever you can handle. </item>
        <item>Sometimes it\'s impossible to get through a day, but you can get through a minute...and minutes add up.</item>
        <item>Your life is meant for a special unique human, who is no one else but you. And you are good enough for it, you are worth.</item>
        <item>The future comes...you just get through the present. </item>
        <item>Just focus on progress, not perfection</item>
        <item>Don\'t let others ruin your accomplishments. They don\'t have that power over you. </item>
        <item>Good luck! Get some rest, you\'ll be great.</item>
        <item>You can do this! One step at a time x</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
